Inventory of the Papers of Duke and Duke 1854-1956
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Case Files
  - 1950's
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. cases against C. Tunstall, William L. Moore, Harold Roberts, W. E. Bray, J. Smith Mawyer, Robert W. Richardson, Bernard O. Bishop, Jr., Elizabeth W. Clark, Effie Maupin, Otto Beninghone, William H. Breeden, Harry H. Pace, Alvis C. Haney, Louise C. Key, Ernest Donovan, Louis F. Lively, Nancy Cleary, Charles L. Woodson, S. A. Lewis, and Carter Martin 1949-1950 (Box 124)
    - Walker v. Jackson 1950 (Box 124)
    - Walker v. Graves 1951-1952 (Box 124)
    - Walker v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1952 (Box 124)
    - Waller v. New Culpepper Mills, Inc. 1950 (Box 124)
    - Walton v. Laird and Co. 1951 (Box 124)
    - Warren v. Hoffman 1951 (Box 124)
    - Watson v. Sears Roebuck and Co. 1951 (Box 124)
    - Watson v. Watson 1952 (Box 124)
    - Earl Weaver 1950 (Box 124)
    - Weaver v. Saunders Electric Co. 1951 (Box 124)
    - Weaver v. Short 1952 (Box 124)
    - Williams v. Barlow 1951-1952 (Box 124)
    - Willis v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951-1952 (Box 124)
    - Wood v. Kostoff 1950 (Box 124)
    - Wood v. Gibson 1950-1951 (Box 124)
    - Woodman v. Wilkerson 1950 (Box 124)
    - Woodson v. Higginbotham 1950 (Box 124)
    - Notes re federal procedure and certain cases 1935-1941 (Box 125)
    - Legal notes and certificate of exceptions 1939-1942 (Box 125)
    - Legal notes especially re Rives estate, Brisco estate, and insurance business 1930's-1940's (Box 125)
    - Legal notes, court proceedings 1940-1943 (Box 125)
    - Looseleaf notebook re lumber account; rules of procedure c. 1941 (Box 125)
    - Forms of instructions especially re auto accidents 1930's (Box 125)
    - California jury instructions 1940 (Box 125)
- Legal Documents
  - Deeds 1885-1899, 5 folders (Box 126)
  - Deeds 1919-1929, 6 folders (Box 127)
  - Abstracts of Title 1876-1889, 11 folders (Box 128)
  - Forms, especially for titles and deeds c. 1890 (Box 129)
  - Abstracts of Title 1890-1897, 8 folders (Box 129)
  - Abstracts of Title 1898-1905, 7 folders (Box 130)
  - Abstracts of Title 1906-1917, 12 folders (Box 131)
  - Notes on deeds, from title searches 1907-1917 (Box 131)
  - Abstracts of Title 1918-1920 (Box 132)
  - Abstract to title of Monticello, Jefferson M. Levy, owner 1920 (Box 132)
  - Abstracts of Title 1921-1922, 2 folders (Box 132)
  - Abstracts of Title--rough drafts 1922-1923 (Box 132)
  - Abstracts of Title 1923, 2 folders (Box 132)
  - Old abstracts--notes 1923-1924 (Box 132)
  - Abstracts of Title 1924-1928, 5 folders (Box 132)
  - Locations of abstracts of title 1910-1920's (Box 132)
  - Abstracts of Title 1932, 1936, 2 folders (Box 132)
  - Legal documents re the following: 1837-1905 (Box 133)
    - Hardesty v. Ficklin 1873-1881, 2 folders (Box 133)
    - Christian v. Rose 1882 (Box 133)
    - Buskirk v. Ferrell 1888 (Box 133)
    - L. Hensley account 1889-1890 (Box 133)
    - Lyon patents 1891 (Box 133)
    - W. C. Sturgill settlement 1891 (Box 133)
    - French v. Trigg 1891-1892 (Box 133)
    - Read v. Dingess 1892 (Box 133)
    - Morris brief 1894 (Box 133)
    - King v. Blankenship 1894 (Box 133)
    - Mora v. Page re Kountze estate 1895 (Box 133)
    - King v. Doolittle 1897 (Box 133)
    - Kentucky v. Lawson 1898 (Box 133)
    - Mace P. Hall estate 1903-1904 (Box 133)
    - Hudson v. Richards 1905 (Box 133)
  - Legal documents re the following: 1902-1930 (Box 134)
    - Thomas J. Coles 1902-1907 (Box 134)
    - Temple v. King Lumber Co. 1905-1907 (Box 134)
    - Walker v. Burgess 1908 (Box 134)
    - R.T.W. Duke, Jr. tax receipts 1909 (Box 134)
    - Carter Page estate 1909 (Box 134)
    - Goodloe estate 1910 (Box 134)
    - Carr v. Ballard 1910 (Box 134)
    - Horner and Co. v. Hult and Co. 1910 (Box 134)
    - Payne insurance policy 1910-1911 (Box 134)
    - Longfield v. Longfield c. 1916 (Box 134)
    - Naturalization certificates 1909-1917 (Box 134)
    - M. R. Flynn account 1919 (Box 134)
    - Boling v. Western Assurance Co. 1925 (Box 134)
    - Davis and Dawson notice of motion 1925 (Box 134)
    - Huttig Mfg. Co. v. Boyle-Robertson Construction Co. 1928 (Box 134)
    - Timberlake v. Marshall 1928 (Box 134)
    - Hyde-Murphy Co. v. Boyle-Robertson Construction Co. 1928 (Box 134)
    - Ellis P. Arthur insurance policy 1929 (Box 134)
    - B. E. Wheeler and R. L. Thomas 1930 (Box 134)
    - Wills 1894-1925 (Box 134)
  - Documents re the following coal companies: 1902-1928 (Box 135)
    - Pike County Coal Co. 1889-1910 (Box 135)
    - Tug River Coal and Coke Co. 1889-1902 (Box 135)
    - Breathitt Coal Co. v. Train 1889 (Box 135)
    - Elkhorn Coal and Coke Co. c. 1890 (Box 135)
    - Ohio and Big Sandy Coal co. 1890-1897, 3 folders (Box 135)
    - Kentucky Coal Co. 1895-1911, 2 folders (Box 135)
    - Blackberry Coal Co. 1902 (Box 135)
    - Logan County Coal and Coke Co. 1902 (Box 135)
    - Pigeon Creek Coal and Coke Co. 1902 (Box 135)
    - Wolf Creek Coal Co. 1902 (Box 135)
    - Crockett's Cove Coal and Iron Co. 1921-1928 (Box 135)
  - Miscellaneous documents re coal business: 1889-1902 (Box 136)
    - Duke account with Kountze Bros. 1888-1894 (Box 136)
    - Breathitt Coal Co. c. 1889 (Box 136)
    - E. Gaujot account 1889-1895 (Box 136)
    - Companies' documents re mineral rights 1889-1896 (Box 136)
    - Sandy River coal field 1890 (Box 136)
    - Dumas v. DeHue; LaCoutre v. Randall; Randall v. Dressler 1891 (Box 136)
    - Land for West Virginia School Fund 1891 (Box 136)
    - Logan County, W. Va estate 1891-1894 (Box 136)
    - Tug Mountain coal property 1894 (Box 136)
    - Coal land acquisition 1894-1903 (Box 136)
    - C. L. Gaujot letter re coal property 1896-1900 (Box 136)
    - Pinkerton letter for Ashbridge 1899 (Box 136)
    - Duke for coal trustees 1900-1902 (Box 136)
    - Coal company proxies 1912 (Box 136)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents c. 1800-1870's, 7 folders (Box 137)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents, especially searches and notes 1870-1920 (Box 138)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents 1870's-1880's, 5 folders (Box 138)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents 1880's-1890's, 6 folders (Box 139)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents 1890's-1920's, 7 folders (Box 140)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents 1910's-1930's, 6 folders (Box 141)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents 1920-1930, 7 folders (Box 142)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents 1939-1960, 4 folders (Box 143)
  - Undate fragments of documents [c. 1870-1920], 3 folders (Box 143)
  - Miscellaneous instructions to jury 1950-1953 (Box 143)
  - Lawyer's Annotated Notes: legal definitions and citations compiled by RTWD 1897-1900 (Box 144)
  - Scrapbook: reports of cases, especially from the Supreme Court of Appeals of Virginia 1892-1895 (Box 144)
  - Negligence law scrapbook c. 1930's (Box 144)
  - Forms for legal documents 1920's-1930's (Box 145)
  - "Abstract book:" copies of titles with indexes for 1928 and 1953 1921-1928, 1953 (Box 145)
- Financial Records
  - Bills, receipts, notes 1900-1928 (Box 146)
  - Statements re Jefferson M. Levy Account 1922-1923 (Box 146)
  - Incoming correspondence re loan accounts--F-L 1922 (Box 146)
  - Accounts payable ledger-- A-E 1922-1925, 2 folders (Box 146)
  - Ledger sheet samples 1927 (Box 146)
  - Accounts receivable 1930-1939, 5 folders (Box 146)
  - Bills 1912 (Box 147)
  - Bills, accounts, etc. 1919-1931 (Box 147)
  - Bills, especially for RTWD, Jr. 1923-1930's (Box 147)
  - Miscellaneous office bills, receipts, cash book notations 1923-1928 (Box 147)
  - Paid bills--A-Z 1925, 2 folders (Box 147)
  - "To be answered"--unopened bills and correspondence 1925-1930 (Box 147)
  - Bills 1927-1928; 1931, 2 folders (Box 147)
  - Miscellaneous unopened bills 1931-1950, 4 folders (Box 148)
  - Bank statements 1916-1917 (Box 148)
  - Checks, deposit slips, vouchers, etc. 1926 (Box 148)
  - WED--Lawyer's time sheets 1927 (Box 148)
  - Tally slips 1941 (Box 148)
  - Western Union bills and receipts 1930-1932 (Box 148)
  - Telephone and telegraph bills 1947-1950 (Box 148)
  - Alphabetical bond files--A-Z 1915-1932, 2 folders (Box 149)
  - Bond for C.C. VanEmon 1928 (Box 149)
  - Bonds and investment records 1929-1930 (Box 149)
  - Paid bonds 1929-1940, 2 folders (Box 149)
  - Miscellaneous bonds and investment records 1920-1940, 2 folders (Box 149)
  - Collection records 1914-1917, 4 folders (Box 150)
  - Applications for loans c. 1922 (Box 150)
  - Naille loan 1927 (Box 150)
  - Loan notebook 1920-1929 (Box 150)
  - Collateral for loans 1930 (Box 150)
  - Forms for letters c. 1920's-1930's (Box 150)
  - Roberta Lewis loan 1950 (Box 150)
  - Rent accounts, especially Yuter 1919-1936 (Box 150)
  - Rent accounts 1932 (Box 150)
  - Financial records for Kountze Bros. 1910-1934, 13 folders (Box 151)
  - Note register 1922-1929 (Box 152)
  - Notes renewed 1925 (Box 152)
  - Notes paid in full 1924-1936 (Box 152)
  - Notes paid 1927-1940 (Box 5 folders)
  - RTWD individual receipts 1872-1886 (Box 153)
  - Receipts 1898, 1911, 1913, 1923-1925, 4 folders (Box 153)
  - Tax statement as of RTWD, Jr.'s death (8 March 1926) 1926-1934 (Box 154)
  - Income tax returns 1921-1922 (Box 154)
  - Income returns for taxes purposes 1924 (Box 154)
  - Income tax returns 1928-1929 (Box 154)
  - Miscellaneous notes and form re tax returns 1923-1928 (Box 154)
  - Taxes miscellaneous 1920's (Box 154)
  - Fiduciary tax returns 1936-1953, 2 folders (Box 154)
  - Forms for U.S. Commissioner's fees 1922-1924 (Box 154)
  - Financial records re divorce cases 1873-1912 (Box 155)
  - Financial records re estate settlements 1880's-1930's, 4 folders (Box 155)
  - Vouchers for Updike v. Johnson 1886-1897 (Box 155)
  - Notices of public sales of estates 1897-1940 (Box 155)
  - Estate accounts 1925-1936, 3 folders (Box 155)
  - Miscellaneous materials found loose in oversize financial records, primarily re insurance cases, but also re case work and personal matters 1870's-1950's (Box 156-157)
  - Bound Financial Records in Oversize Boxes 1884-1908; 1946
    Arranged by size
    - Sandy River [Coal] Field 1890 (Box 158)
    - Sandy River Coal Field 1890-1894 (Box 158)
    - Miscellaneous coal business 1888-1890 (Box 158)
    - Southeastern Kentucky coal land business 1890-1892 (Box 158)
    - Catlettsburg National Bank 1890, 2 vols. (Folder 158)
    - Luther Kountze re coal land 1888-1889 (Box 158)
    - National Bank and Trust Co. (Mary Duke) 1946 (Box 158)
    - Bank of Albemarle re Wingfield v. Wingfield 1904 (Box 158)
    - People's National Bank re Peyton v. Gilbert 1898-1899 (Box 158)
    - People's National Bank re E.D. Sampsone estate 1884-1885 (Box 158)
    - William P. Farish estate 1881-1908 (Box 158)
    - Indexes for Kentucky coal land abstracts 1889-1890 (Box 158)
    - Kentucky Coal Co. minutes 1903-1923 (Box 158)
    - Miscellaneous estate accounts 1872-1899, 2 vols. (Box 158)
    - Carry R. Randolph estate 1885-1904 (Box 158)
    - M. Andre Burthe estate 1929-1931, 2 vols. (Box 158)
    - Frederick G. Rust estate account 1896-1918 (Box 158)
    - Account books for Duke and Duke 1881-1919, 10 vols. (Box 159)
    - Daily account of receipts, with some notations re recent judgements 1898 (Box 159)
    - Notes re loan and estate accounts c. 1924 (Box 159)
    - Laon account book 1922-1923 (Box 159)
    - "Bills payable" 1925-1931 (Box 159)
    - Notebook of WRD containing parts of a ledger and records of contracts 1888-1889 (Box 159)
    - Mileage register of WED 1947 (Box 159)
    - Notes re trust funds and bonds (Mary Duke) c. 1919-1927 (Box 159)
    - Personal cash book for Mary Duke 1939-1941 (Box 160)
    - Petty cash ledger n.d. (Box 160)
    - Register of fee accounts with some notes re case materials, especially Low v. Holt 1944 (Box 160)
    - Minutes of University Motors stockholders' meetings 1933-1935 (Box 160)
    - Index to claims and collection cases 1925-1939 (Box 161)
    - Collection docket with notes 1929-1932 (Box 161)
    - Case docket, includes "office judgements" 1867-1874 (Box 161)
    - Case dockets re suits for debt 1865-1875 (Box 161)
    - Account book for Duke rental property 1903-1911 (Box 161)
    - Ledger for Clermont Hotel 1923-1930 (Box 161)
    - Suit and collection record with names of witnesses, authorities and notes 1901-1910 (Box 162)
    - Collection dockets 1878-1891, 2 vols. (Box 162)
    - Accounts for George Shackelford 1872-1873 (Box 162)
    - Ledger for Big Bill Bottling Co. 1926-1928 (Box 162)
    - Ledger for Edith and RTWD, Jr. estates 1926-1939 (Box 163)
    - Ledger for insurance and bonds for Duke family members 1907-1917 (Box 163)
    - Collection docket, fee accounts arranged by case 1893-1898 (Box 163)
    - Ledger for Duke and Duke fee accounts 1946-1948 (Box 163)
    - Ledger for estate accounts arranged by client name 1926-1928 (Box 164)
    - Fee book and cash accounts 1875-1879 (Box 164)
    - Account book 1939-1941 (Box 164)
    - Insurance companies' instructions and forms 1920's-1930's (Box 164)
    - Loan accounts ledgers arranged by client names 1922-1932, 2 vols. (Box 165)
    - Bond registers 1909-1924, 2 vols. (Box 165)
    - Ledger re stock purchases and paid dividends arranged by client 1890-1897 (Box 166)
    - Ledger for estate accounts and bond records, includes Miller Board records 1903-1917 (Box 166)
    - Register of insurance policies arranged by client 1924-1927 (Box 166)
    - Fee book for Duke and Jones (1871) and ledger for estate and fee accounts 1870-1874 (Box 167)
    - Ledger for fee accounts, commissioner's fee, and expense accounts 1880-1897 (Box 167)
    - Fee accounts arragned by client; expense accounts arranged by years 1895-1908 (Box 167)
  - Bound Financial Records on Shelves
    Arranged numerically
    - Jefferson Hotel Register 1930-1931 (Oversize 1)
    - Accounts for an orchard business 1924 (Oversize 2)
    - Ledger for Armstrong Knitting Co. 1896-1899 (Oversize 3)
    - Cehck and loan account register for Duke, Duke and Gentry 1922-1926 (Oversize 4)
    - Cash book for Duke, Duke and Gentry 1922-1925 (Oversize 5)
    - "Cash book"/ledger 1923-1924 (Oversize 6)
    - Ledger--F-Z 1925 (Oversize 7)
    - Fee accounts 1888-1895 (Oversize 8)
    - "Day book and journal," fee account book and ledger 1909-1918 (Oversize 9)
    - "Trial balance" ledger 1919-1928 (Oversize 10)
    - Collection docket and court record 1878-1896 (Oversize 11)
    - Bond register for American Surety Co. 1912-1921 (Oversize 12)
    - Deposits record for RTWD, Jr. 1922-1927 (Oversize 13)
    - "Day book" and loan accounts 1918-1923 (Oversize 13)
- General Office Correspondence and Cases
  - Desk diaries for WED 1928-1953, 10 vols. (Box 168)
  - Wall calendar with notations 1953 (Box 168)
  - Office memoranda: daily notes prepared for WED 1947-1953, 7 folders (Box 169)
  - Advertisements 1930's-1940's, 2 folders (Box 170)
  - Albemarle County Road Matters 1916-1920 (Box 170)
  - American Law Book Co. 1934 (Box 170)
  - Armstrong Knitting Co. 1901 (Box 170)
  - Attorney's Case Dockets c. 1922-1925, 2 folders (Box 170)
  - Authorities c. 1923 (Box 170)
  - B 1922-1953, 3 folders (Box 170)
  - Ba 1947 (Box 170)
  - Be 1943 (Box 170)
  - Bi 1933 and n.d. (Box 170)
  - Boiling Springs Property Sale 1880-1882 (Box 170)
  - Channing M. Bolton and Albemarle Telephone Co. 1898-1902 (Box 170)
  - William H. Bowcock, Knights of Honor 1870-1920 (Box 170)
  - Fannie A. Brisco estate 1924-1934 (Box 170)
  - E. B. Brown 1900 (Box 170)
  - John E. Buck 1925 (Box 170)
  - Harry F. Byrd 1933-1935, 1940 (Box 170)
  - C 1924-1953, 2 folders (Box 171)
  - Ca to Ch1923 (Box 171)
  - George H. Carey 1925-1931 (Box 171)
  - W. F. Carter estate 1926-1953 (Box 171)
  - Catalogues 1927 (Box 171)
  - Clients [miscellaneous unfiled correspondence] 1940's (Box 171)
  - Cogswell and Co. vouchers 1895-1901 (Box 171)
  - Bernard Coles 1928-1929 (Box 171)
  - Edward Coles 1874 (Box 171)
  - Collecton docket, attorney's docket 1937 (Box 171)
  - Commercial Clearing House 1929 (Box 171)
  - Corporation forms c. 1920's-1930's (Box 171)
  - Court papers, some re cases 1927-1928 (Box 171)
  - A. D. Cox 1897-1898 (Box 171)
  - Moses Crawford 1949 (Box 171)
  - W. E. Crenshaw 1925-1943 (Box 171)
  - Current Legal Thought 1937 (Box 171)
  - Dailey and Co. 1932 (Box 171)
  - Dairy Bar; B. W. Anderson 1938-1944 (Box 171)
  - A. H. Davin 1924-1942 (Box 171)
  - Deeds--rough notes 1905-1920 (Box 171)
  - Division of Statutory Research and Drafting; William R. Shands 1931-1937 (Box 171)
  - RTWD, Jr.'s "important papers" 1905-1906 (Box 171)
  - Dorothy S. Dulin 1946-1951 (Box 171)
  - Dorothy Earp loan account 1934 (Box 171)
  - Edgehill property sale--correspondence, broadside, vouchers 1877-1878 (Box 171)
  - E 1930-1952, 3 folders (Box 172)
  - Ediphone 1929-1943 (Box 172)
  - Ejectment--notes 1953-1954 (Box 172)
  - Thomas W. Ellett 1926 (Box 172)
  - Ended matters 1922-1924 (Box 172)
  - F 1931-1946, 1952 (Box 172)
  - F 1931-1946, 1952 (Box 172)
  - Falconer 1946 (Box 172)
  - Federal clerk's office 1924 (Box 172)
  - Federal Gas, Oil and Coal Co. 1946 (Box 172)
  - Forms 1920's-1940's, 2 folders (Box 171)
  - Friday 1927-1929 (Box 172)
  - Garrison-Via land matter 1934, 1938 (Box 172)
  - C. E. Gentry 1921-1928, 5 folders (Box 172)
  - Henry Gibbs 1923-1924 (Box 172)
  - Go 1930-1941 (Box 172)
  - L. W. Graves, Jr. 1930-1934 (Box 172)
  - G 1920-1943, 2 folders (Box 173)
  - T. Irving Hadden 1930-1931 (Box 173)
  - Hagood v. Hagood [1924] (Box 173)
  - Hancock v. Morse n.d. (Box 173)
  - Oskar J. W. Hansen 1936-1937 (Box 173)
  - W. A. Harris 1919-1924 (Box 173)
  - He 1933-1938 (Box 173)
  - Hi 1930-1938 (Box 173)
  - Huckstep and Burnett 1927 (Box 173)
  - Hu 1930-1940 (Box 173)
  - H 1950 (Box 173)
  - I 1953 (Box 173)
  - Kardex divisions 1929 (Box 173)
  - K 1953 (Box 173)
  - Lafferty Farm 1936-1944 (Box 173)
  - Laird and Co. 1947 (Box 173)
  - W. A. Lambeth 1924 (Box 173)
  - Land transactions 1928 (Box 173)
  - Larkin Company 1923 (Box 173)
  - Belle D. Layne 1903-1920's (Box 173)
  - Ledgers, forms 1920's (Box 173)
  - Wayne F. Lee 1923 (Box 173)
  - Legal Clearance Corporation [?] 1952 (Box 173)
  - Legal form notebook 1951-1953, 3 folders (Box 173)
  - Legal notes c. 1931, 1947-1948, 3 folders (Box 174)
  - Letterheads 1940's-1950's (Box 174)
  - Letters not sent 1933, 1948 (Box 174)
  - Letters to sign, examine 1932 (Box 174)
  - Jefferson M. Levy 1923 (Box 174)
  - Lineweaver Motor Co. 1922-1923 (Box 174)
  - Li 1930-1940 (Box 174)
  - Loan accounts 1930-1931 (Box 174)
  - Lockwood Mfg. Co. 1923 (Box 174)
  - Loose office correspondence 1937 (Box 174)
  - Mary Lupton Estate 1930 (Box 174)
  - Susan Lupton Estate 1917-1919 (Box 174)
  - L, miscellaneous 1923-1942, 2 folders (Box 174)
  - James U. McClammer 1948 (Box 174)
  - H. R. McIlwaine 1923-1926 (Box 174)
  - Marion McKay 1924 (Box 174)
  - L. W. McVeigh 1923 (Box 174)
  - John L. Manahan 1923 (Box 174)
  - Manhattan Stationary Co. 1927-1930 (Box 174)
  - J. L. Miller n.d. (Box 174)
  - S. C. Miller 1923 (Box 174)
  - William Miller 1922 (Box 174)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence re cases 1910-1928 (Box 174)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and documents c. 1883-1925 (Box 174)
  - Mi 1930-1938 (Box 175)
  - Bessie Lee Morris, re Bettie S. Brent 1920-1924 (Box 175)
  - Mountain Land 1933-1934 (Box 175)
  - William B. Murphy 1923 (Box 175)
  - M 1923-1924, 2 folders (Box 175)
  - National Credit Corporation 1925-1926 (Box 175)
  - National Savings and Trust Co. 1923 (Box 175)
  - Wilbur A. Nelson 1930-1935 (Box 175)
  - Nichols and Hargrave 1923 (Box 175)
  - Noland Co. 1923 (Box 175)
  - Notary public commission 1946-1951 (Box 175)
  - Notes 1923 (Box 175)
  - Notes re cases 1930's-1940's (Box 175)
  - Notes and exams on constitutional law and federal procedure c. 1910-1925, n.d. (Box 175)
  - Miscellaneous handwritten notes, fragments of documents, etc. 1920's and 1940's, 2 folders (Box 175)
  - Nuchapep, Inc. 1924-1928 (Box 175)
  - N 1923, 1930-1931, 2 folders (Box 175)
  - Office equipment ads 1925-1926 (Box 175)
  - Office records, loan accounts, etc. n.d. (Box 176)
  - Office supplies 1950-1953 (Box 176)
  - "Old mail" 1928-1929 (Box 176)
  - Outgoing letters 1938-1940, copies (Box 176)
  - Albert P. Owsley 1923 (Box 176)
  - O 1923 (Box 176)
  - Passports 1920's (Box 176)
  - Pending claims 1922-1925, 2 folders (Box 176)
  - Pending file 1927-1928 (Box 176)
  - "Pending--Mr. Duke's matter" 1931-1938 (Box 176)
  - Pending work 1927 (Box 176)
  - H. P. Porter 1931, 1944-1945, 2 folders (Box 176)
  - Ramsey Probasco 1922-1924 (Box 176)
  - Process--extraordinary writs 1923 (Box 176)
  - Proofs 1912 (Box 176)
  - Public Service Corp., County of Albemarle 1916 (Box 176)
  - P 1952 (Box 176)
  - Questionnaires c. 1936 (Box 176)
  - Q 1930 (Box 176)
  - J. H. Reid 1923-1926 (Box 176)
  - Retail Credit Company 1928 (Box 177)
  - Ringbook notes, letters for signature 1949 (Box 177)
  - J. M. Rothwell 1952 (Box 177)
  - Rough drafts of briefs, notes 1930's (Box 177)
  - R 1952 (Box 177)
  - A. J. Smith and E. O. Smith 1898 (Box 177)
  - R. W. Stewman 1923 (Box 177)
  - S. W. Stover Estate 1871-1874 (Box 177)
  - S 1950's (Box 177)
  - Tax forms 1930's-1940's (Box 177)
  - Tax returns, bonds, conveyancing 1926-1945 (Box 177)
  - "To file" 1927-1928 (Box 177)
  - "Unfiled" 1920-1931 (Box 177)
  - United States Bond and Mortgage Co. 1915 (Box 178)
  - U.S. Navy Supply bids re timber 1942 (Box 178)
  - University Cafe 1927-1928 (Box 178)
  - V 1950's (Box 178)
  - Marion Wiatt 1921-1925 (Box 178)
  - I. B. Wenger, Jr. 1923-1925 (Box 178)
  - B. E. Wheeler 1922-1930 (Box 178)
  - The White System Co. 1923 (Box 178)
  - Carroll M. Wood and Ada M. Wood 1922-1923 (Box 178)
  - Matilda Woods 1924-1926 (Box 178)
  - Woodson and Woodson 1923 (Box 178)
  - John Zellars Account 1936-1953 (Box 178)
  - W, X, Y, Z1954 (Box 178)
  - Undated Business Correspondence [1870-1920] (Box 178)
  - Unfiled papers, including correspondence re cases and other business matters, documents, bills (many unopened), etc. Most of the personal papers were found with these materials and were culled. When case materials were recognized, they were interfiled in the proper place. 1880's-1950's, 32 folders (Box 179-182)
  - Accident material, unidentified n.d. (Box 183)
  - Allstate 1943-1952 (Box 183)
  - Allstate subrogation claims 1949 (Box 183)
  - American Surety Company 1922-1937, 3 folders (Box 183)
  - Henry Erving Batcheller 1923 (Box 183)
  - Hubert R. Brown, American and Canadian Insurance counsel 1931 (Box 183)
  - W. F. Carter, Jr. 1923-1927 (Box 183)
  - Commercial Casualty Insurance Co. 1927-1932, 3 folders (Box 183)
  - Consolidated Indemnity and Insurance Co. 1929 (Box 183)
  - Constitution Indemnity Co. 1932 (Box 183)
  - Continental Casualty and Insurance Co. 1924-1954, 3 folders (Box 183)
  - Employers of Wassau 1935-1937 (Box 183)
  - Government Employees Insurance Company 1939 (Box 183)
  - Great American Insurance Company 1924 (Box 183)
  - Hartford Accident and Insurance Company 1939 (Box 183)
  - Illinois Manufacturers' Mutual Casualty Association 1933 (Box 183)
  - Imperial Accident Assurance Company 1929 (Box 183)
  - Independent Indemnity Company 1923-1924 (Box 183)
  - Insurance Bar Decisions 1936-1943 (Box 184)
  - Insurance Claim Journal 1930 (Box 184)
  - Insurance Company Business 1925-1930 (Box 184)
  - Insurance Forms, especially for workmen's compensation cases 1930's-1940's, 4 folders (Box 184)
  - Insurance pamphlets, advertisements c. 1923 (Box 184)
  - Insurance receipts 1922 (Box 184)
  - Keystone Automobile Club Casualty Company 1946-1954 (Box 184)
  - Marsh and McLennan, Inc. 1937 (Box 184)
  - Metropolitan Casualty Insurance Company 1930-1931 (Box 184)
  - Mutual Plate Glass Insurance Company 1930 (Box 184)
  - New Amsterdam Casualty Group 1923 (Box 184)